Guide to the New York Building Congress Records WAG.167
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: General Files, 1918-2011; 486309
  - New York City Commissioner of Buildings: Candidates, 1983; 486464 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - New York City Comptroller, 1985; 486463 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - New York City Construction Outlook (NYBC), 2000-2007; 486462 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - New York City Construction Outlook (NYBC), 2008-2009; 486461 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - New York City Council: Codification Committee, 1967; 486460 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - New York City Department of Buildings, 1980; 486459 (Box 14, Folder 33a)
  - New York City Department of Buildings Reorganization: Mayor John V. Lindsey Correspondence, 1966; 486458 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - New York City Department of Buildings Reorganization: Meetings, 1966; 486457 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - New York City Department of Design and Construction (proposed): Task Force, 1995-1996; 486456 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - New York City Department of General Services: Upcoming Projects, 1993-1994; 486455 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - New York City Department of Housing Preservation and Development: Correspondence, 1979-1982; 486454 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - New York City Department of Transportation: Bridge Programs, 1983; 486453 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - New York City Department of Transportation: Report, 1993; 486452 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - New York City Departments Reorganization (Mayor Lindsay's Plan), 1966-1967; 486451 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - New York City Economic Policy and Marketing Group: Job Creation Strategies, 1993; 486450 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - New York City: Executive Budget, 1982; 486449 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - New York City Housing and Development Administration, 1973; 486448 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - New York City Housing Partnership, 1982; 486447 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - New York City Housing Partnership: Land Development Guide, 1990; 486446 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - New York City Office of Director of Construction, 1978; 486445 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - New York City Office of Management and Budget, 1991; 486444 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - New York City Public Development Corporation: Financial Planning and Analysis Scope of Services, 1982; 486443 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - New York City: Rezoning, 1986; 486442 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - New York City School Construction Authority, 1989; 486441 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - New York City School Construction Authority, 1996; 486440 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - New York City Service Crisis: A Management Response, 1989; 486439 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - New York City Transit Authority, 1983; 486438 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - New York City Transportation Administration: Manhattan Truck Route Study, 1977; 486437 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - New York Construction, Jan 2011; 486436 (Box 15, Folder 12a)
  - New York Construction News, 1955; 486435 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - New York Construction News, 1987; 486434 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - New York Construction News, 1992; 486433 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - New York Construction Users Council, 1982; 486432 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - New York Construction Users Council, Undated; 486431 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - New York Interagency Engineering Committee, 1982; 486430 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - New York Society of Association Executives, 1988; 486429 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - New York Society of Association Executives: Government Affairs Committee, 1986; 486428 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - New York Society of Association Executives: Government Affairs Committee, 1987; 486427 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - New York Society of Association Executives: Government Affairs Committee, 1988; 486426 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - New York Society of Association Executives: Government Affairs Committee, 1989; 486425 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - New York State Advisory Commission to the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights: "Discrimination in the Building Trades", 1963; 486424 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - New York State Organized Crime Task Force: Corruption and Racketeering in the New York City Construction Industry, 1987; 486423 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - New York State Power Authority: Report on Hydroelectric Power, circa 1980; 486422 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - New York State Society of Professional Engineers, 1982; 486421 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - New York State Society of Professional Engineers, 1985; 486420 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - New York State Temporary Commission on Lobbying, 1988-1989; 486419 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - New York World's Fair (1964-1965), 1961; 486418 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - News and Issues (NYBC Newsletter), 2003-2006; 486417 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - NYC2012 (Olympic Bid), 2002-2004; 486416 (Box 15, Folder 31a)
  - Perkins Eastman Architects: 10th Anniversary Pamphlet, 1994; 486415 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Port Authority Agenda Letter, 1989; 486414 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey: Truck Commodity Survey, 1986; 486413 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Pratt Institute: New York City Building Laws Seminar, Undated; 486412 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Press Coverage of NYBC, 1986-1987; 486411 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Press Coverage of NYBC, 1988; 486410 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Press Coverage of NYBC, 1989; 486409 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Press Coverage of NYBC, 1995-1999; 486408 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Press Coverage of NYBC, 2005-2008; 486407 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Press Coverage of NYBC, Undated; 486406 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Press Releases, 1946, 1952; 486405 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Press Releases, 1986-1988; 486404 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Press Releases, 1989; 486403 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Press Releases, 1995-1996; 486402 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Press Releases, 2000-2007; 486401 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Press Releases, Undated; 486400 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Pride: St. Louis Construction Industry Labor-Management Coalition, 1975-1977; 486399 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - "Problems of Discrimination and Extortion in the Building Trades:" Report, Koch Administration, 1982; 486398 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Promotional Material, 1922; 486397 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Promotional Material, 1942; 486396 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Promotional Material, 1981, 1986-1987; 486395 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Promotional Material, 1990, 1994; 486394 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Promotional Material, Undated; 486393 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Public Relations Board, 1969; 486392 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Public Relations: Correspondence, 1978; 486391 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Public Relations: Correspondence, 1986; 486390 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Public Relations: Correspondence, 1987-1989; 486389 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Public Relations: Correspondence, 1994; 486388 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Publications, NYBC, 1941-2010; 486387 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Publicity, 1987-2007; 486386 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Real Estate Board of New York, 1984-1986; 486385 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Real Estate Board of New York: Don McGuirk's Talk to, 1982; 486384 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Real Estate Institute, New York University, 1982; 486383 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Real Estate Weekly, Issue Covering Trade Associations, 1988; 486382 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Rebuilding America Conference (I), 1994; 486381 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Rebuilding America Conference (II), 1994; 486380 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Rebuilding America Conference, 1995; 486379 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Rebuilding New York Initiative, 1986; 486378 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - "Region's Cities: an Underground Report," by Peter Goldmark, Port Authority, 1981; 486377 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Regional Alliance for Small Contractors, 2005; 486376 (Box 15, Folder 70a)
  - Regional Plan Association, 1987; 486375 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Regional Plan News, Sep 1982; 486374 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Rent Stabilization Association, 1980; 486373 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - "Report of the Commission on the Year 2000", 1987; 486372 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Resource Recovery Program: New York City Sanitation, 1981-1982; 486371 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Roofing and Waterproofing Contractors Association, 1990; 486370 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - St. John the Divine: Crane Purchase, Jul 1981; 486369 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Seelye Stevenson Value and Knecht, 1971; 486368 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Site Safety, 1983; 486367 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Site Safety, 1986; 486366 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Site Safety, 1988; 486365 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Society of the Plastics Industry, 1982; 486364 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - South Street Seaport (pamphlet), Undated; 486363 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Special Report: "Virtual Design and Construction", 2008; 486362 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Speeches (Dandrow), 1955; 486361 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Speeches (John J. Collins), 1976; 486360 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Speeches (To Construction Finance Manager's Association), 1988; 486359 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Staten Island Naval Base Homeport Project, 1986; 486358 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Steamfitting Industry Promotion Fund, 1988; 486357 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Steel Shortage, 1973; 486356 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Study of the New York City Building Code (Brooklyn Polytechnic), 1961; 486355 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Subcontractors Trade Association, 1984-1987; 486354 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Summit Meeting (Real Estate/Construction), Mar 1992; 486353 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Task Force on Capital Financing and Construction: Other "Three R's": Rebuilding, Renewing, and Reinvesting in the New York City Public Schools, 1989; 486352 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Taxpayer Action Lawsuit: Schulz v. State of New York, 1995; 486351 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Teacher Awards Luncheon (New York Alliance for the Public Schools), 1988; 486350 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Testimony (To New York State Division of Human Rights), 1977; 486349 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Testimony (To New York City Council, Committee on Economic Development, Louis Coletti), 1990; 486348 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Testimony (Richard T. Anderson), 1995-2009; 486347 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Testimony (Others), 1998-2006; 486346 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Traffic Congestion and Clean Air Act Requirements, 1986; 486345 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Trans Hudson Express Tunnel (pamphlet), circa 2006; 486344 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Truck Weight Study, 1980; 486343 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - U.S. House of Representatives, Subcommittee on Economic Development, 1993; 486342 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Velez Organization, 1995; 486341 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Waste Disposal, 1973-1974; 486340 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Waste Disposal Problem in New York City: Proposal for Action, 1984; 486339 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Waterfront Comprehensive Plan Advisory Committee, 1991; 486338 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - West Side Highway Position Paper, 1989; 486337 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - West Side Transitway Planning and Feasibility Study: Working Papers, 1989; 486336 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Westway, Undated; 486335 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Westway: Clippings, 1983-1985; 486334 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Westway: Correspondence, 1977; 486333 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Westway: Correspondence, 1978; 486332 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Westway: Correspondence, 1982; 486331 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Westway: Correspondence, 1983; 486330 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Westway: Correspondence, 1984; 486329 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Westway: Correspondence, 1985; 486328 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Westway: New York Citizens for Balanced Transportation, 1981-1986; 486327 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Westway: Press and Publicity, 1976, 1979; 486326 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Westway: Press and Publicity, 1982; 486325 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Westway: Press and Publicity, 1983; 486324 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Westway: Press and Publicity, 1984; 486323 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Westway: Press and Publicity, 1985; 486322 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Westway: Public Notices, 1982; 486321 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Westway: Report by Kenneth Clark, 1984; 486320 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Westway: West Side Highway Replacement Study, 1986; 486319 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - "What's Happening on the Waterfront?" (Report, New York City Department of Ports and Terminals), 1983; 486318 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - "Wicks Law Reform", 1981; 486317 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Wolfe, Tom: From Bauhaus to Our House (Interview re:), 1981; 486316 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Zoning, 1968-1971; 486315 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Zoning: Fifth Avenue, 1971; 486314 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Zoning: Second Avenue Subway, 1969-1971; 486313 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Zoning: Special Transportation Districts, 1968; 486312 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Zoning Resolution: Proposed Amendments, 1958-1960; 486311 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Zoning Resolution: Proposed Amendments, 1960-1963; 486310 (Box 16, Folder 62)
- Series IV: Events, 1938-2010; 486103
  Series IV: Events, 1938-2010 contains the records of the many events organized by the NYBC. The material on the Christmas shows and "Fun and Frolic" shows is particularly rich. There is also substantial material on the NYBC's 50th Anniversary celebration and the 1995 breakfast forums.
  - Anniversary (25th), 1938; 486308 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Anniversary (25th), 1946; 486307 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Anniversary (40th): General, 1961; 486306 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Anniversary (40th): Memos and Correspondence, 1961; 486305 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Anniversary (50th): Attendees and Seating Lists, 1971; 486304 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Anniversary (50th): Budget, 1971; 486303 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Anniversary (50th): Committee, 1971; 486302 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Anniversary (50th): Correspondence, 1971; 486301 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Anniversary (50th): General, 1971; 486300 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Anniversary (50th): Memos, 1971; 486299 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Anniversary (50th): New York Times Sunday Supplement, 1971; 486298 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Anniversary (50th): New York Times Sunday Supplement, Requests for, 1971; 486297 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Anniversary (50th): Speeches, 1971; 486296 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Anniversary (50th): Sponsors, 1971; 486295 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Anniversary (60th), 1982; 486294 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Anniversary (70th), 1991; 486293 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Anniversary (75th), 1996; 486292 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Annual Meetings, 1978; 486291 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Annual Meetings, 1980-1986; 486290 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Annual Meetings, 1987; 486289 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Annual Meetings, 1988; 486288 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Annual Meetings, 1989-1990; 486287 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Annual Meetings, 1991; 486286 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Annual Meetings, 1995-1996; 486285 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Annual Meetings, 2001-2010; 486284 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Breakfast Forum, 1994; 486283 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Breakfast Forum (Kaladjian), Jan 1995; 486282 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Breakfast Forum (Gelber), Feb 1995; 486281 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Breakfast Forum (Stasch), Mar 1995; 486280 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Breakfast Forum (Gargano), Apr 1995; 486279 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Breakfast Forum (Downs), May 1995; 486278 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Breakfast Forum (Powers, Schwartz), Jun 1995; 486277 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Breakfast Forum (Hevesi), Jul 1995; 486276 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Breakfast Forum (Membership Seminar), Sep 1995; 486275 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Breakfast Forum (Conway), Sep 1995; 486274 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Breakfast Forum (Vallone), Oct 1995; 486273 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Breakfast Forum (Hunter), Nov 1995; 486272 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Breakfast Forum (Ferrer), Dec 1995; 486271 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Breakfast Forum, 1995; 486270 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Breakfast Forum, 1996; 486269 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Breakfast Forum: Agendas, 2000-2010; 486268 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Breakfast Forum: Invitations, 2000-2007; 486267 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Breakfast with New York City Council, 1996; 486266 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Building Industry Forum, 1981; 486265 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Christmas Luncheon, 1939; 486264 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Christmas Show, 1940; 486263 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Christmas Show, 1941; 486262 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Christmas Show, 1942; 486261 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Show, 1943; 486260 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Christmas Show, 1944-1945; 486259 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Christmas Show, 1946; 486258 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Christmas Show, 1947; 486257 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Christmas Show, 1948; 486256 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Christmas Show, 1950-1951; 486255 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Christmas Show, 1952; 486254 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Christmas Show, 1953; 486253 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Christmas Show, 1954; 486252 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Christmas Show, 1955; 486251 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Christmas Show, 1956; 486250 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Christmas Show, 1957; 486249 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Christmas Show, 1958; 486248 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Christmas Show, 1959; 486247 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Christmas Show, 1960; 486246 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Christmas Show, 1961; 486245 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Christmas Show, 1962; 486244 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Christmas Show Titles (List) with Lyrics, 1938-1973; 486243 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Comptroller Candidates Meeting, Jul 2009; 486242 (Box 18, Folder 19a)
  - Conference: Business/Labor, 1993; 486241 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Conference: Contractors, 1989; 486240 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Conference: Energy, 1979; 486239 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Conference: Indoor Air Quality, 1988; 486238 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Conference: Rebuilding New York, 1987; 486237 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Conference: Rebuilding New York, 1988; 486236 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Conference: Smoke Toxicity, 1990; 486235 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Conference: Taiwan and New York/New Jersey Design and Construction Industry, 1992; 486234 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Conference: Urban Design, 1988; 486233 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Construction Industry Colloquium on Infrastructure, 1996; 486232 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Construction Industry Forecast Seminars, 1987-1988; 486231 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Construction Industry Forum: Speaker, Host, and Venue List (2004-2011), 2010; 486230 (Box 18, Folder 30a)
  - Construction Industry Summits, 1994-1996; 486229 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Construction Trade Show: Correspondence, 1987; 486228 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Construction Trade Show: Correspondence, 1988; 486227 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Construction Trade Show: Correspondence, 1989; 486226 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Construction Trade Show: Correspondence, 1990; 486225 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Construction Trade Show: Press and Publicity, 1981-1983; 486224 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Construction Trade Show: Press and Publicity, 1987; 486223 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Construction Trade Show: Press and Publicity, 1988; 486222 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Construction Trade Show: Press and Publicity, 1989; 486221 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Construction Trade Show: Press and Publicity, 1990; 486220 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Dinkins-Stein Debate, 1981; 486219 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Dinner: Industry Recognition, 1996; 486218 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Dinner: Industry Recognition, 1998-2006; 486217 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Dinner: Industry Recognition, 2007; 486216 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Dinner: Industry Recognition, 2008; 486215 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Dinner: Industry Recognition, 2010; 486214 (Box 19, Folder 10a)
  - Dinner: Industry Recognition - Chairman and Guest(s) of Honor List (1996-2010), 486213 (Box 19, Folder 10b)
  - Dinner: Max Foley Jubilee, 1949; 486212 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Dinner: New York Building Foundation Premier Wine Dinner, 2008; 486211 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Event Schedules, 1989; 486210 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Fun and Frolic: Cartoon Ad Winners, 1947-1970; 486209 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Laugh, Labor, Lunacy! or Why Not?", General, Dec 1963; 486208 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Laugh, Labor, Lunacy! or Why Not?", Cartoon Book, Dec 1963; 486207 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Laugh, Labor, Lunacy! or Why Not?", Costumes, Dec 1963; 486206 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Laugh, Labor, Lunacy! or Why Not?", Script and Playbill, Dec 1963; 486205 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Fun and Frolic: "It Ain't Fair Lady, or Where's the Dough?", Cartoon Art, Dec 1964; 486204 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Fun and Frolic: "It Ain't Fair Lady, or Where's the Dough?", Costumes, Dec 1964; 486203 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Fun and Frolic: "It Ain't Fair Lady, or Where's the Dough?", General, Dec 1964; 486202 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Fun and Frolic: "It Ain't Fair Lady, or Where's the Dough?", Rehearsal Memos, Dec 1964; 486201 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Fun and Frolic: "It Ain't Fair Lady, or Where's the Dough?", Script, Playbill, Dec 1964; 486200 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Blackouts of 1965! or Niagara Fails," Cartoon Book, Dec 1965; 486199 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Blackouts of 1965! or Niagara Fails," General, Dec 1965; 486198 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Blackouts of 1965! or Niagara Fails," Playbill, Dec 1965; 486197 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Blackouts of 1965! or Niagara Fails," Rehearsal Memos, Dec 1965; 486196 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Fun and Frolic: "This is the Year that was," General, Dec 1966; 486195 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Fun and Frolic: "This is the Year that was," Script and Playbill, Dec 1966; 486194 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Fun and Frolic: 1967 Show, General, Dec 1967; 486193 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Trouble is Building or Some Days are for Striking", Dec 1968; 486192 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Fun and Frolic: "No Nudes is Agnewds," General, Dec 1969; 486191 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Fun and Frolic: "A.ll F.or L.ove C.ash I.s O.ut or We Can Dream Can't We?", Dec 1970; 486190 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Fun and Frolic: 50th Anniversary Show, Mar 1971; 486189 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Fun and Frolic: 50th Anniversary Show, Script, Mar 1971; 486188 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Let Me Make it Perfectly Clear or HELP," Book, Dec 1972; 486187 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Let Me Make it Perfectly Clear or HELP," Script, Dec 1972; 486186 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Fun and Frolic: "The Man Who Came to Lunch," General, Dec 1973; 486185 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Oh What a Beautiful Morning or Cheers," Costumes, Dec 1974; 486184 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Oh What a Beautiful Morning or Cheers," General, Dec 1974; 486183 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Oh What a Beautiful Morning or Cheers," Script, Dec 1974; 486182 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Fun and Frolic: 1975 Show, Script, Dec 1975; 486181 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Up, Up or Oi Vey," General, Dec 1976; 486180 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Fun and Frolic: "We're Bouncing Back-You Too!!!", Script and Rehearsal Schedule, Dec 1978; 486179 (Box 20, Folder 1a)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Don't Look Back, Give the 80's a Whack," General, Dec 1979; 486178 (Box 20, Folder 1b)
  - Fun and Frolic: 1980 Show, Script, Dec 1980; 486177 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Fun and Frolic: "How About You?", General, Dec 1981; 486176 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Fun and Frolic: "How About You?", Script, Dec 1981; 486175 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Fun and Frolic: 60th Anniversary Show, General, Mar 1982; 486174 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Fun and Frolic: 60th Anniversary Show, Program, Mar 1982; 486173 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Fun and Frolic: "All for Love or Cash is Out," General, Dec 1982; 486172 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Fun and Frolic: 1983 Show, Script, Dec 1983; 486171 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fun and Frolic: "No Endangered Species or Live in '85", Dec 1984; 486170 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Fun and Frolic: "No SNAFU or the Construction Connection", Dec 1985; 486169 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Fun and Frolic: "Let Me Make it Perfectly Clear or HELP", Dec 1986; 486168 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Fun and Frolic: "'87 and Beyond or Let's Go B.C.", Dec 1987; 486167 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Fun and Frolic: Unknown Show, Undated; 486166 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Fundraiser for Brian McLaughlin, 1996; 486165 (Box 20, Folder 14)